&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：如果你有一个像9号线那样非常疯狂的呼叫站点怎么办？
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: What if you had a really crazy call site like line 9?
在第9行，我有一个新的关键字，我有一个车间点问，所以
On line 9, I have a new keyword, I have a workshop dot ask, so
我有一个上下文对象。
I have a context object.
并且我有点绑定，当然在封面下使用应用。
And I have dot bind, which under the covers of course using apply.
我的四个规则中有三个在相同的调用站点上匹配。
I have three of my four rules matched on the same call site.
顺便说一句，我并不是建议你写一个这样的呼叫站点，但是
I am not by the way suggesting you should ever write a call site like that, but
真的有用。
it does actually work.
那么，它到底为什么会工作，它是如何知道使用哪种东西的呢？
So why on Earth does it work, and how does it know which thing to use?
如果有多个规则与一个调用地点匹配，优先顺序是什么？
If more than one rule matches a call site, what's the order of precedence?
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：嗯，有一种方法可以说服你自己或者
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Well, there's a way that you could convince yourself or
向自己证明操作的顺序或优先顺序是什么。
prove to yourself what the order of operations, or the order of precedence is.
但我还是先简化一下，然后告诉你，
But I'm just gonna go ahead and simplify, and tell you,
这就是问这些问题的顺序。
this is the order to ask those questions.
所以从现在开始，如果你需要问自己我的关键词是什么
So from here forward, if you ever need to ask yourself what is my thisKeyword
指出这个函数何时被调用，这就是你如何确定的。
gonna point out when this function gets invoked, this is how you determine that.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：这个关键字的确定是，第一，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: The determination for the thisKeyword is, number one,
函数是用new调用的吗？
was the function called with new?
如果是，则新创建的对象将是thisKeyword。
If so, the newly created object will be the thisKeyword.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：第二，函数是通过调用还是应用来调用的？
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Number two, is the function called with a call or apply?
顺便说一下，点绑定是该规则的子规则，因为它也使用apply。
And by the way dot bind is a sub of that rule because it also uses apply.
如果是，则将使用指定的上下文对象。
If so, the context object that is specified will be used.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：如果不匹配，那么第三个，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: If that doesn't match, then number three,
这个函数是在上下文对象上调用的吗，比如工作坊的dot ask？
is the function called on a context object like workshop dot ask?
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：如果是这样，请使用该对象。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: If so, use that object.
如果这三个都没有应用，那么我们回退到默认的
And if none of those three have applied, then we fall back to the default which
表示默认为全局对象，但在严格模式下除外。
says default to the global object except in strict mode.
就是这样，就是这四条规则的顺序，它将完美而完整地
That's it, just those four rules in that order, and it'll perfectly and completely
回答你可能有的关于我的关键字指向什么的所有问题？
answer every question that you may have about what does my thisKeyword point at?